{
    "id": "5b796d897902451787276d154507d6d8",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She is prettier ……………………. anybody I know.",
            "description": "Better is a comparative word. It is followed by than.",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "then",
                "compared to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3276d904b817479c91db46f11dd744fa"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have hardly done ………………………… since morning.",
            "description": "Hardly is a negative word. It cannot be used with nothing.",
            "answers": [
                "anything",
                "nothing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "40f13789b8dd4d45b24383e6afc8ab20"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have …………………………. met any film stars.",
            "description": "Never is used in affirmative sentences.",
            "answers": [
                "ever",
                "never"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "dafc0982611d4618880e8041bb51b1ae"
        },
        {
            "question": "Have you …………………………….. been to Australia?",
            "description": "In questions we use ever.",
            "answers": [
                "ever",
                "never"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c5f5e31890bf403aa1eba2e975873cf8"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is difficult to understand ………………………… she says or does.",
            "description": "Non-assertive words like anybody and anything are mainly used with words expressing a negative kind of meaning.",
            "answers": [
                "anything",
                "nothing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f2edb554cf0f40b69860e65cfdf311a2"
        },
        {
            "question": "The pilots went on strike, but …………………………… the air hostesses.",
            "description": "To make a word, expression or clause negative, we use not.",
            "answers": [
                "not",
                "no",
                "none"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "358449dd70c04a759aa86e6bb92a7bc3"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. teachers went on strike.",
            "description": "No can mean not any.",
            "answers": [
                "No",
                "Not",
                "None"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5bbe2c9c033b4c7cbbcbfbcfd5231f1c"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………… you say, I will not believe you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "No matter what",
                "Whatever",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "99b529cb268e496ea672f9a3084be729"
        },
        {
            "question": "Call me when you arrive, ………………………………. late it is.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "no matter how",
                "however",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "cacae3e7a2f8499b9ac2b3248c000ad9"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is ……………………….. a great artist than I am.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "anymore",
                "no more",
                "nomore"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "926009f0bae44b61b70ddb56a1be6a1d"
        },
        {
            "question": "It takes ……………………………. to get used to driving in the city.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a long time",
                "long time",
                "long"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6ad7d1a2b33b43b5add7aee3209d1f03"
        },
        {
            "question": "You look ………………………….. What happened?",
            "description": "Look is a copular verb. It is modified by an adjective. ",
            "answers": [
                "sad",
                "sadly"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c98644809e114f97ae968ea9fca059de"
        }
    ]
}